A Guide to the Rockefeller Family Public Relations Department papers, Series 13 FA1193
Rockefeller Archive Center
- "New President for a Growing Sleepy Hollow", 1986 May 11 (Box 22, Folder 275)
- JDR, Jr., "I Believe" Quote (Box 23, Folder 276)
- The Rockefeller State Park Preserve, Brochure and Map (Box 23, Folder 277)
- Sleepy Hollow Restorations, Brochures, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 278)
- Brochures; Riverside Church Carillon, Greenacre Park, The Cloisters (Box 23, Folder 279)
- Rockefeller Brothers Fund, Planning Committee Report, 1983 October (Box 23, Folder 280)
- The Win Rockefeller Story (Box 23, Folder 281)
- Rockefeller, Nelson A., Index Listing, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 282)
- Rockefeller, Nelson A., Art, 1964, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 283)
- Rockefeller, Nelson A., Awards, Degrees, and Honors, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 284)
- Rockefeller, Nelson A., Biographies and Associations, 1950-1951, 1955, 1958, 1960, 1964, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 285)
- Rockefeller, Nelson A., Books on Governor Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 286)
- Rockefeller, Nelson A., Chronology, Highlights of Positions Governmental and Business (Box 23, Folder 287)
- Rockefeller, Nelson A., Congressional Quarterly, Public Record of Governor Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1967 July 21 (Box 23, Folder 288)
- Rockefeller, Nelson A., Conservation, Clean Water & Air, Recreation & Culture, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 289)
- Rockefeller, Nelson A., Memberships and Clubs, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 290)
- Rockefeller, Margaretta F., Articles on Happy Rockefeller, 1968-1969, 1974-1975, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 291)
- Rockefeller, Nelson A., Divorce, 1961 (Box 23, Folder 292)
- Rockefeller, Nelson A., Associations, Cultural, Business, and Governmental, 1968 July 16 (Box 23, Folder 293)
- Rockefeller, Nelson A., Personal Information, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 294)
- Rockefeller, Nelson A., Personal Information, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 294A)
  Restricted-Confidential material
- Rockefeller, Nelson A., Farms, 1958-1960, 1962-1963, 1965, 1967-1968, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 295)
- Rockefeller, Nelson A., Presidential Appointments, 1968 June (Box 23, Folder 296)
- Rockefeller, Nelson A., Republican National Committee Sketch, 1968 June (Box 23, Folder 297)
- Rockefeller, Nelson A., Report and his Government Security Clearance, 1955, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 298)
- Rockefeller, Nelson A., Statement of Non-Candidacy & Candidacy, 1968 March 21 & April 30 (Box 23, Folder 299)
- Rockefeller, Nelson A., Possessions, Personal, Real Estate, 1958-1964, 1967-1969, 1974-1975 (Box 23, Folder 300)
- Rockefeller, Nelson A., Political Newspaper Clippings, 1968, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 301)
- Rockefeller, Nelson A., Directories, 1949-1969 (Box 24, Folder 302-303)
- Rockefeller, Nelson A., Confirmation Hearings, Laurance S. Rockefeller Statements, 1974 November 9 & 15, December 4 (Box 24, Folder 304-306)
- Rockefeller, Nelson A., Confirmation Hearings, Nelson A. Rockefeller's Opening Statement, 1974 November 21 (Box 24, Folder 307)
- Rockefeller, Nelson A., Confirmation Hearings, J. Richardson Dilworth Statement, 1974 December 3 (Box 24, Folder 308)
- Rockefeller, Nelson A., Confirmation Hearings, John A. Wells Statement, 1974 November 15 (Box 24, Folder 309)
- Rockefeller, Nelson A., Swearing In Statements, 1975 January-February (Box 24, Folder 310)
- Rockefeller, Nelson A., Vice President Nomination and Swearing In, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 311)
- Rockefeller, Nelson A., Death Related Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 25, Folder 312)
- Rockefeller, Nelson A., Memorial Service Materials, 1979 February 2 (Box 25, Folder 313)
- Rockefeller, Nelson A., Private Family Burial, 1979 January 29 (Box 25, Folder 314)
- Rockefeller, Nelson A., Memorial Booklet Distribution Materials, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 315)
- Rockefeller, Nelson A., Memorial Service Booklets, 1979 February 2 (Box 25, Folder 316)
- Rockefeller, Nelson A., Correspondence and Photographs on Memorial Booklet, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 317)
- Rockefeller, Nelson A., Memorial Booklet Distribution List, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 318)
- Rockefeller, Nelson A., Memorial Service, Notice List, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 319)
- Rockefeller, Nelson A., Memorial Service, Press and Riverside Church Arrangements, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 320)
- Rockefeller, Nelson A., Memorial Service, Eulogies, 1979 February 2 (Box 26, Folder 321)
- Rockefeller, Nelson A., Note References, Death, 1979-1980 (Box 26, Folder 322)
- Rockefeller, Nelson A., Note References, Death, 1979-1980 (Box 26, Folder 322A)
- Congressional Record, 1979 January 29, 31, February 5-7 (Box 26, Folder 323-325)
- Congressional Record, 1979 February 8-9, 15, 22 (Box 27, Folder 326-327)
- Harrison, Wallace K., Death, Related Materials, 1981-1982 (Box 27, Folder 328)
- Harrison, Wallace K., Related Materials, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 329)
- Milton, David Meriwether, Memorial Service, 1976 July 9 (Box 27, Folder 330)
- Rockefeller, Winthrop, Interment Service at Rockefeller Family Cemetery, 1981 June 13 (Box 27, Folder 331)
- Mauze, Abby Rockefeller, Obituary, 1975-1976 (Box 27, Folder 332)
- Haupert, Anna, Memorial Service, 1984 October 3 (Box 27, Folder 333)
- Scrivner, Robert, Memorial Service, 1984 May 16 (Box 28, Folder 334)
- Rockefeller, John D., IV, Senate Campaign, West Virginia, 1977, 1981, 1983-1984 (Box 28, Folder 335-337)
- Doherty, Criena, Interview, 1979 March (Box 28, Folder 338)
- Rockefeller, Nelson A., Post Death, Newspaper Clippings, 1979 February (Box 28, Folder 339)
- Rockefeller, Nelson A., Media Coverage, Newspaper Clippings, 1979 February 16 (Box 28, Folder 340)
- Pierce, Ponchitta & Megan Marshack, Newspaper Clippings, 1979 February-March (Box 28, Folder 341)
- Marshack, Megan, Newspaper Clippings, 1979 Fenruary (Box 28, Folder 342)
- Billings Farm & Museum, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 343)
- Union Theological Seminary, Brochure, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 344)
- Rockefeller, Nelson A., Art, Newspaper Clippings, 1978-1979 (Box 29, Folder 345)
- Pocantico Properties, Newspaper Clippings, 1969-1970, 1976, 1978-1979, 1981-1982 (Box 29, Folder 346)
- Rockefeller, Laurance S., Honored by Palisades Interstate Park Commission, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 347)
- Kykuit Lithographs, Sketches and Photographs, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 348)
- Rockefeller, Laurance S., Ketch Photographs, 25 years of Service Presentation, 1984 September 21 (Box 29, Folder 349)
- Pocantico Hills Properties, Semi-Final Report on Land Planning, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 350)
  - Pocantico Hills Properties, Semi Final Report on Land Planning, 1962 (Box 30, Folder 357)
    Separated Materials
    Oversized maps
- Rockefeller Family Fund, Printing Awards, Printing Industries, 1973-1974, 1976-1977 (Box 30, Folder 351)
- Rockefeller, Laurance S., Ottauquechee, A National Prototype (Box 30, Folder 352)
- Rockefeller, Laurance S., Resolutions Presented to Laurance S. Rockefeller, 1987 December 22 (Box 30, Folder 353)
- Rockefeller, Laurance S., Honorary Member of Princeton Class of 1973, 1983 June (Box 30, Folder 354)
- Rockefeller, Laurance S., Arnold Newman Photographs, 1969 April (Box 30, Folder 355)
- Unidentified Portrait (Box 30, Folder 356)
- Stock Prices, P/E Rations, and the Stock of Money, 2017:FA1193:003; Large oversized graph on stocks, tracing paper